好的，现在我们有个艰巨的任务了。把
All right, here's a big one. Finish
SyncAdapter 完成，用它来获取天气数据，
the SyncAdapter, making it fetch the weather
并且储存在数据库中。
and store it in the database. Alter
在ForecastFragment中需要修改updateWeather函数
the updateWeather function within the ForecastFragment to
使用SyncAdapter进行同步处理。这里需要注意一些点
start a sync with the SyncAdapter. Some things here. Pull the code from on
把onHandleIntent方法的代码放进SyncAdapter中。onHandleIntent方法
handle intent into our SyncAdapter. On handle
在我们的Sunshine服务里。
intent is inside of our Sunshine service.
这样做的好处是AbstractThreadedSyncAdapter（SyncAdapter的基类）
The good news is that abstract threaded
会提供一个后台线程，来处理
sync adapter provides a background thread to
从服务器端获取的数据，就像是
run the server fetch on, just like
Intent服务一样。 类似的，可以从utility类中
intent service does. Also, just fetch the location
提取地点请求。最后，我们
query from our utility class. Eventually, we
想要在无用户参与的情况下进行同步操作
want to run syncs like this without any
最后的最后，确保SyncAdaptor会在我们
involvement of the user. Finally, make the
调用Update Weather之后运行。
sync adaptor run when we call Update Weather.